Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana, was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad also possess powers from the devils of the Underworld,
and use them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
Ooh, I just had a great idea. Hey Megicula, let's not kill her after all.
Oh? Then why is that?
She's the wisdom of the Heart Kingdom. I thought it best to eliminate her.
Eh, who cares about that stuff?
We should take her back to Spain with us!
By the way, Noelle, I just remembered I did fight some lady with armor like yours.
What was her name?
Oh yes, Asiere! She was so much fun!
And as I recall, her powers got super strong when she saw that I took some poor little kid hostage.
So if I kidnap Laura Petschka here, then I can only assume you would get a lot stronger too!
I can't pretend that I understand this feeling, but you're desperate to protect her because she's your friend, right?
None of our people are going to mind, so I say we go for it.
You know, Vanica, you're so full of surprises, it's great!
Well, now that's decided, I guess we're done here.
Poor Petschka! And Noelle!
What is it, my lady? We're leaving for the Spain Kingdom already?
Do you think we could wait a minute or two? I've almost got this little beauty right where I water it!
Don't talk to me, you're disgusting.
As a matter of fact, I have no use for you anymore.
Curse-warding magic exploding life!
His mom is expanding!
Wait! Lady Vanica! What do I... you...
This is what's called a curse bomb!
That devil's power I gave you, Dark Disciples?
Well, it's just about to go...
Boom, thing, crash now!
No! What's happening to me?
You wouldn't, would you?
Please don't, Lady Vanica! I beg you!
This whole area's gonna blow sky high!
But I'm sure you can survive that, right, tough girl?
And when you do, I'll be waiting for you in spade!
Get strong for me!
Fare thee well!
My little Noelle!
Vanica!
C'mon!
What?
BANG!
Gonna wait in it for the brand new world!
Yeah!
We gonna take you to the brand new world!
To the brand new world!
We gonna wait in it for the brand new world!
Get your hands up, baby!
We gotta take you to the black hour
Oh, yeah!
They drowned out!
Get it on! Get it on!
始めよう!
難航不落のリアリティ
立ち止まる時間はないさ
Hold on! Hold on!
Yeah!
Now this time, fight for liberty
真実性 飲み込み常識
Oh, yeah!
逆転は先にある朝
健闘に埋もれた人生の夢
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えて
もうかすぐして
Feel it!
We gotta pay!
Let's go!
Leave it myself!
衝動的に突き進め
Don't be afraid
誰よりも高く飛べ
Take it to the sky
想像を超えた世界をこの手に
The ground up!
想像性偽りどない自分の道
Yes! It's a ground up!
Hey, yeah!
Believe in myself!
Believe in yourself!
Hey, yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
Death mountain!
AVAILABLE NOW
Oh, my God.
The kid's anti-magic is the key to winning this.
Somehow we gotta land a hit on that guy with Asta's sword.
I'm holding him back. I know I am.
Captain Yami is the only reason I'm not dead yet.
Even with six months of training, I'm still no match for this guy.
Don't give up now.
Keep the attacks coming.
I'm ecstatic. You have no idea what an immense pleasure this is for me.
I may not understand these powers I have inside, but our only hope is for me to use them at full blast.
Hey, you've been watching, right? Devil?
What the heck are you doing?
I can't believe you didn't say that to me. I've been in Asta's dragon for a while now.
Right, I remember.
We've met like this before, but you seem different this time.
I'll kill them. Kill them all.
They must be killed.
Kill.
Earlier, I could feel your rage welling up.
I don't know your reasons, but you want to beat this guy too, don't you?
I should have had a real heart-to-heart with you a long time ago, so I could understand you better.
No time like the present.
Come on, lend me your powers.
Hurry!
Okay, sure. I guess I can let you take my true strength for a little spin.
Zap the evil who won't be thinks the way they are.
I'll need you to give me something equal in return.
In return?
You're gonna let me take a part of your body.
Remember, you're making a deal with a devil.
No matter what it takes, even if it means becoming a devil, I have to push past my limits.
I'm gonna need backup over here.
Asta?
Captain Yami said those words.
It meant everything in the world to me.
If I can't get through this, then I'll never become the Wizard King.
You know, kid, I like you. Come join our crew.
And then, once we're done, you go and become the Wizard King.
I will, Captain Yami.
But before I do that,
I want to prove I've become the person you always hoped I would be.
All right, it's a deal.
Knock yourself out.
Gravity magic.
Gravity singularity.
As of right now,
You should know that right arm isn't the same as it was back when I was just giving you a little power at a time.
Now it's become power.
You've got 50 seconds till your body gives out.
That's funny!
It's not funny!
It's not
What do I want
Am
It's not
Such marvelous work!
I can tell from the way he's fighting.
He's on guard when Asta attacks.
That must be anti-magic coming from his right arm.
If he can get at least one decent hit in there,
we can win this.
Show him what you're made of, Asta!
He's crushing it.
Better step up my game.
Let's show him together.
What's that supposed to do?
Excellent fighting technique, you two.
But don't stop.
Give me more!
Excellent fighting technique, you two.
But don't stop.
Give me more!
Asta?
Yummy!
I know you're not done yet.
Keep the entertainment coming!
Look at them.
They're moving.
That's awesome.
I know you're not done yet.
Keep the entertainment coming!
Look at them.
They're moving insanely fast.
But they're totally in sync.
Thanks!
Despite everything, they actually look like they're having fun.
Fight me.
Fight with all you've got.
It won't matter because in the end, I will crush everything!
You've already lost!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Dweller!
Destroy us!
You're mine!
I am immortal!
This is the end!
The end for you!
Looks like we haven't lost after all.
Well done, Nasta. You crazy son of a bitch. Thanks.
That was incredible! You totally took him down!
I mean, wow! That battle! It was amazing!
Yeah, I guess so.
Damn straight it was.
Did...
You beat him?
What happened?
Gosh...
You didn't die!
Thank goodness!
You're really okay!
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry!
What are you apologizing for?
Yeah...
Something is up with those two for sure.
Going somewhere?
What's up?
He may be out of commission now.
Even dying.
But we should tie him up to be safe.
Oh! Good point!
I'm glad we're finally finished with this psycho stalker.
I've got better ways to spend my time.
Though...
We did capture the enemy's top devil possessed.
So I guess it's happily a...
Man, I am officially beat.
I can't wait to collapse on the bed.
No!
Yummy!
Screwed up.
He's got me pinned.
Who is that?
And there.
It's the captain of the Golden Dawn.
The key to the underworld isn't you, per se.
It's a magical channel known as the Tree of Klyphoth.
To bring that channel into being, we need dark magic and world tree magic, both at the arcane stage.
So this was the source of the magic fluctuation I was sensing.
There's no salvation for them.
We hold existence itself in the palms of our hands.
You gave a speech like that, then lost.
What a pathetic leader you turned out to be.
A spatial magic user.
You bastard!
I'm still feeling the effects of my previous fight.
Fortunately, he shouldn't be a problem anymore.
I'd have liked to take this one too, but time's up.
Over my dead body!
Don't let him get away!
The world will end.
Captain!
Please!
Devil!
I'll let you claim another part of my body if that's what it'll take!
Please!
I need to borrow your powers again!
No!
Your mind can't even move anymore!
It doesn't matter how desperate you want to keep fighting!
You wouldn't be able to handle another deal!
So that's it then...
No deal...
That's right!
Because you're weak!
Fineral!
A portal!
Go, Rouge!
Meow!
Just touch the Captain once!
That's all that'll take!
No!
Me!
I left...
Oh God...
Mother!
Captain Yami, no!
Beautiful
夜明け前の空 静かにそっと
ほら新たな日々が始まる
胸にしまい込んだままの想いを解き放って
その翼を広げて One more time
今飛び立て あの海原を見落として
誰よりも遠く 何度でも Will you fly?
Beautiful
どんな景色も 君といれば輝くよ
だからずっとそばにいて
And never let go
僕のこの手を 離さないで
どこまでも ついてきてほしい
The world is so beautiful
We've gotten what we need from the Clover Kingdom
No! They have Yami!
What are we supposed to do now?
Black Clover, page 168
Stirrings of the Strongest
We've been an experienced
Z